NURUL ISNAINI, S.Pd

Teacher

+62 813 3466 4737



@nurisna777

isnaininurul87@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

My name is Nurul Isnaini. People usually call me Ms Isna. Iam 36 years old. Iam from East Java, but I stay in Lampung for a job. Iam an English teacher of SMAN 1 Negara Batin, Way Kanan - Lampung. I've been a teacher for 15 years.

I define myself as a lifelong learner. No matter how old I am and wherever I am, doing self-improvement is a must. Everyone is a teacher, everyone is a student, and everywhere is a school.

EDUCATION



2004 -2008 : UNIPMA (Universitas PGRI Madiun), Faculty of Language and Art,

Majoring in English Education.

2001 - 2004 : MAN Ngawi (Science)

1998 - 2001 : MTsN Ngraho - Bojonegoro

1991 - 1997 : SDN Sumberjo 03, Margomulyo - Bojonegoro

Informat

Oct 2022 - July 2023 : Pendidikan Guru Penggerak Angkatan 7

(Balai Guru Penggerak Prov. Lampung)

August 2022 - Oct 2022 : Google Master Trainer Level 1, Batch 7

(Ditjen GTK in collaboration with REFO and

Google for Education)

15th - 19th of Dec 2020 : Workshop Media Pembelajaran Online Mata Pelajaran

Bahasa Inggris

November 2017 : Pendidikan dan Latihan Profesi Guru (PLPG)

July 13-15, 2012 : Pendidikan dan Pelatihan Penyusunan Perangkat

Pembelajaran dan Model Pembelajaran

Nov 25, - Dec 9, 2010 : Pendidikan dan Pelatihan Jabatan Pegawai Negeri

Sipil (PNS)

November 15, 2015 : Diklat Nasional "Implementasi Model Cooperative Learning

dalam Pembelajaran Karya Tulis Ilmiah"

• EXPERIENCE

2010 - Now : English Teacher of SMAN 1 Negara Batin

Responsible for developing English Club Program for Students

July 2022 - Dec 2022 : Responsible for PMR Program in SMAN 1 Negara Batin

Jan 2021 - Sept 2022 : English Tutor in Private course "EDA's Course "Kec. Negara Batin

Nov 21 - Nov 26, 2021: Guru Magang Dinas Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan Provinsi Lampung

July 12 - Sep 9, 2017 : Guru Pamong in Praktik Lapangan Terpadu FKIP UNILA

(English Subject)

2008 - 2009 : English Teacher in SDN Sumberjo 01 Margomulyo - Bojonegoro

English and Math Teacher in SMPN Satu Atap Kalangan, Margomulyo

Margomulyo

• SKILL

- English (Active and Passive)
- Computer (Ms Office)
- Design Graphic, especially CANVA
- Google for Education
- Creative